Contact

alybama76@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alyson-mullinax-9babbba1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medical Education Leadership Teamwork

Certifications
Registered Nurse

Alyson Mullinax

Operating Room Travel RN

Fort Payne, Alabama

Summary

Nineteen years of experience in the medical field with sixteen of those being a Registered Nurse. Experience in multiple areas of health care, including perioperative services, women's health, pediatrics, surgery, cardiac catheterization lab, emergency services, home health, and hospice.

Experience

Soliant

Operating Room Travel Nurse September 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months) Birmingham, Alabama

Currently working at The University of Alabama at Birmingham Hospital, primarily in Vascular and Neurosurgery.

Gadsden Regional Medical Center Registered Nurse April 2012 - September 2015 (3 years 6 months) Gadsden, Alabama

Pediatrics, Emergency Department, and Operating Room Experience

Highlands Medical Center Registered Nurse April 2013 - October 2013 (7 months) Scottsboro, Alabama

Emergency Department RN, Part-time position while also working at Gadsden Regional Medical Center.

ABC Hospice
Registered Nurse
August 2011 - March 2012 (8 months)

Rainsville, Alabama

Home care provided to terminally ill patients

Community Health Systems
Charge Nurse (RN)
August 2009 - August 2011 (2 years 1 month)
Fort Payne, Alabama

Cardiac Catheterization Lab Nurse

Alabama Department of Public Health Registered Nurse April 2006 - November 2009 (3 years 8 months) Fort Payne, Alabama/ Montgomery, Alabama

Performed home visits to patients unable to leave their homes in need of medical treatment.

Jackson Hospital Charge Nurse (RN) January 2009 - August 2009 (8 months) Montgomery, Alabama

Charge nurse on pediatric floor

Office of Dr. Jeffrey Thompson Registered Nurse September 2004 - April 2006 (1 year 8 months) Fort Payne, Alabama

Surgical scrub nurse for Dr. Jeffrey Thompson and Dr. Terry Jones. Input CPT and ICD-9 codes for biling purposes.

Community Health Systems
Labor and Delivery Tech/ Registered Nurse
April 2000 - September 2004 (4 years 6 months)
DeKalb Regional Medical Center

Labor and Delivery Scrub Tech until after graduating nursing school in 2003. Labor and Delivery nurse until 2004.

Education

Northeast Alabama Community College
Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2001 - 2003)

Troy University
Elementary Education and Teaching · (1997 - 1999)

Enterprise State Community College

General Studies · (1995 - 1997)

Fort Payne High School

High School Advanced Diploma, Advanced Diploma · (1990 - 1994)